Amanda Seals trying to talk about some hip hop.
You know what it is.
The Black Spin.
All right, DJ Supreme, what are we talking about today?
What makes an artist a hip hop artist?
An emcee is somebody who in their music,
the lyricism in their verse is what drives the record,
not just the hook.
So like you look at somebody like Hove, right?
And a lot of people say that he's the greatest of all time.
And I think a lot of the reason is because
he was simultaneously able to have like catchy hooks,
but then verses that made you be like,
oh, you know, that really involved like lyrical prowess.
Drake to me, it's not that Drake is pop.
I think that to me, Drake is kind of versatile, right?
Like Drake is like full on singing
and also doing like rap records.
That to me is more so what makes him pop,
him straddling the line of genre in that way
versus like his actual raps.
I know Drake versus like I've actually like been impressed
by his lyricism on more than one occasion.
Hip hop had the ability to like change the way people thought,
not just the people who loved hip hop,
but the people who had to deal with hip hop
because it existed in the world, right?
It exposed the world to a whole different point of view
around black people.
And I think that when it comes to hip hop
and continuing that tradition,
it's like if you are continuing to have that sensibility
in your music, then you hip hop.